let questions = [
  {
    numb: 1,
    question: "Which of the following is a persuasive technique?",
    answer: "Emotional appeal",
    options: [
      "Emotional appeal",
      "Descriptive language",
      "Narrative structure",
      "Character development"
    ]
  },
  {
    numb: 2,
    question: "What is the purpose of a persuasive text?",
    answer: "To convince the reader of a particular viewpoint",
    options: [
      "To entertain the reader",
      "To inform the reader",
      "To convince the reader of a particular viewpoint",
      "To describe a setting"
    ]
  },
  {
    numb: 3,
    question: "In analytical writing, what is the main focus?",
    answer: "Commenting on a text and expressing opinions",
    options: [
      "Telling a story",
      "Commenting on a text and expressing opinions",
      "Writing a poem",
      "Summarizing a book"
    ]
  },
  {
    numb: 4,
    question: "What does the term 'writer's message' refer to?",
    answer: "The underlying message or theme in a text",
    options: [
      "The author's biography",
      "The underlying message or theme in a text",
      "The plot of the story",
      "The characters in the story"
    ]
  },
  {
    numb: 5,
    question: "In 'Oliver Twist', what can the writer's message be linked to?",
    answer: "The author's intentions and views",
    options: [
      "The setting of the story",
      "The author's intentions and views",
      "The characters' actions",
      "The historical context"
    ]
  },
  {
    numb: 6,
    question: "What is the first stage of Freytag's Pyramid?",
    answer: "Exposition",
    options: [
      "Exposition",
      "Rising action",
      "Climax",
      "Falling action"
    ]
  },
  {
    numb: 7,
    question: "Which part of Freytag's Pyramid involves the main conflict of the story?",
    answer: "Climax",
    options: [
      "Exposition",
      "Rising action",
      "Climax",
      "Resolution"
    ]
  },
  {
    numb: 8,
    question: "What is the purpose of the resolution in a story?",
    answer: "To resolve the conflict and provide closure",
    options: [
      "To introduce the characters",
      "To resolve the conflict and provide closure",
      "To build tension",
      "To describe the setting"
    ]
  },
  {
    numb: 9,
    question: "Which of the following is NOT a persuasive writing technique?",
    answer: "Chronological order",
    options: [
      "Rhetorical questions",
      "Statistics",
      "Chronological order",
      "Anecdotes"
    ]
  },
  {
    numb: 10,
    question: "When planning a short story, what is an important element to consider?",
    answer: "Character development",
    options: [
      "Character development",
      "Length of the story",
      "Number of pages",
      "Type of paper"
    ]
  }
];

export { questions };
